Friends, in 2016, when God Jat came to India,
when they started working in India,
their general insurance,
health insurance, car insurance, then the
company was completely new and in the last seven-eight
years, this company has achieved a different position for itself, the
company has made a different name for itself,
even the big companies
like I am talking about HDFC, Tata,
Tata AG, ICC Lord, I am talking about
motor insurance, then
this company has established itself in
front of these companies and in many cases, this
company, Gadget, is considered better than these companies, so we will
talk
about this company,
what features does this company provide you, what add-ons does it
provide you, subscribe to our channel
because you keep getting notifications of such videos that we make, so
let's start,
now friends, let's talk about
what facilities the company provides you, friends,
here their cashless garages are
more than 6500, if you go anywhere in India,
you will easily find them,
talk about renewal, if  You are getting a
policy from the company, you
can continuously renew the policy as long as you are
using your vehicle. If we talk about policy cancellation, then
policy cancellation
is available but
you get your money back after deducting some charges, so whenever you
cancel the policy, do check it once
and policy cancellation is not such that you
can do it in every condition,
in some conditions only you have to give a legal reason, a
valid reason has to be given, only after that
you can cancel it. You can get this policy for 6
years, so for 7 years, for 8 years,
if your NCB is running then you
can easily get a zero day policy, for 78 years. Let's
talk about first party OD policy,
third party, so you
can get all these three things from the company. If you have a two wheeler,
you have a four wheeler, then you
can take first party, you can take only OD policy,
you can take third party, whatever you
understand in it, you can take it in it, whatever
you require, if you
need only third party then  Whether it's a third-party, first-
party, or OD policy,
you can get it from here.
Their claim settlement ratio is 92 to 96 percent, which is
quite good. You can easily trust this company.
You'll always get a
good claim from here. As far as we've
seen, and our
experience has been,
you get a claim very easily.
You don't have to face much hassle. The
excellent claim service is the same. Claim
service is easy to get, you do
n't face any problems. Many
old companies are operating in India.
I won't name them,
but you won't face any problems with those companies. However, you won't face any problems with new companies that have been
in India for just six years.
Their
services are quite good.
Talking about settlement charges,
you will incur 5 percent settlement charges, which is applicable
in almost all companies. Talking about support, they provide
24/7 support. You
can call them any day, 365 days a week, whether it's a national holiday or a
weekend.  You will always get support
247, their service center,
their call center, is always working.
Now friends, let's talk about
what all things you can get from the company here.
So friends, number one is
third party. You can get it from here for
your two-wheeler, for your four-
wheeler, owner-driver. Friends, I am
talking about two-wheelers. Two-wheeler
cashless garages are separate. And what
I have mentioned for 6500 plus is only
for motor insurance, it is
only for car insurance. So,
in third party, you can add owner-driver. You
can add owner-driver P cover which is a mandatory cover of ₹ lakh. You
can take passenger cover. You can take driver cover.
You will get only these three things in third party:
owner-driver cover, passenger
cover or driver cover. Apart from this, you will
not get anything in third party and
you will get a third party claim of 7.5 lakh in third party
easily if you damage someone,
damage someone's property
or if someone dies due to
your vehicle.
Due to an accident, there is
unlimited cover for it, but if you
damage property, then the
company gives you a claim of up to 75 lakhs.
Apart from this, friends, you can take comprehensive and on-
damage. Friends,
in comprehensive, you get both OD policy and third party.
In on-damage, you get only D
policy. So here you
can take third party, comprehensive,
on-damage policy. Let's
talk to this company about add-ons,
what add-ons do they give you, then here you get road dep.
Here you can take consumables.
Here you can take engine and gear box protection.
Here you get road saat assistant.
You get return to invoice,
tyre cover.
Daily conveyance is available here. If your
vehicle is in the service centre and is under repair,
then you get conveyance there. You get
daily key and lock replacement.
Apart from this, you get person belonging, so
you can get this from the company for your vehicle.
Apart from this, friends, here there are three
such unique  There are features which you
get only in this company, you do
not get them in any other company. Now see what that feature is,
like Pay as you Drive friends, if
you drive your car for less than 15000 km in a year, then the
company gives you an extra
discount, where your premium is
coming for example to 200000, so here
if you drive your car for less than 15000 km, then
your premium will be only 14 to 15
15000, so this is a facility the
company gives you, you have to get a vehicle inspected at the time of renewal,
apart from this let's talk about zero dep number of
claims, friends, all the companies either
give you two claims or one claim
or give you unlimited claims,
in Universal Some Pay you have the option of
one or two claims, otherwise and
in some company you do not get the option to
select your number of claims,
how many number of claims you want, so here the
company gives you limited, you can also make one claim  You
can select that
you get one claim on zero day, you can make two as well
and here you have the option that you
can make unlimited claims as well
in your policy, so friends, this
feature is not available to you in all the
car insurance
policies in India, you do not get this facility in any company, you
can choose as per your choice, you want one claim, you want
two claims, you
want unlimited claims in the same company, then you
will decide, yes but there will be a difference in the premium, it will be a
little higher in the unlimited one and a
little less in the one or two, so there will be this much difference,
apart from this let's talk about discount,
friends, although the agent can give this discount to the
agents if he wants, it is
not necessary that he will do it for you but he
can do it, friends, the company gives them such a
facility that they can
increase the extra discount by some percent in their policy,
although their commission gets reduced a bit in them,
but if the agent wants, it is
not like this in some vehicles, in every vehicle,
in some vehicles, some percentage of discount can be
increased for you.  It
can give you an extra percent discount there
and if you want in any company, then you get only those discounts which are
pre-set according to the vehicle.
Apart from the pre-set discount that you are getting here, the agent can also
reduce your premium a little by increasing the discount here. So
these are three unique things that Go Digit
gives you and gives it in a completely different way.
Apart from this, is there any such company in the industry
which offers you these three things? Now
friends, let's talk about the premium.
How is this premium decided and
how much will it be? Friends, the third party
premium is always fixed, which will be given as per the
guidelines of IRD. The premium will be given as per
your CC, the number of CCs of your vehicle
or how many CCs your two-wheeler is.
Apart from that, let's talk about on-damage.
Friends, if you take a comprehensive policy, then
you get both the things. In one policy,
if you take only on-damage, then you will
get only on-damage. If you take third-party, then
you will get third-party separately. So, if you
take comprehensive, then the premium of both the things comes
together.  You will get separate third party
on-damage insurance. If you take it separately, it will be
different. Now let's talk about
how this premium is decided.
Friends, there is
no single criteria for deciding the premium. There are different things
like NCB. What is your NCB?
If the NCB is less or zero, then
you will get less discount. If the NCB is
more, then you will get more discount.
Now be careful, I have written this
here because apart from the
good digit, in all the companies apart from this, only this
company has one negative point, that too the
calculation of NCB which they do is
a negative point. Their calculation is
completely different and I don't know how they
calculate it, whereas in other companies, the
method of calculation is very simple.
Whatever discount there is,
that amount is written in front of that discount. But
suppose there is a discount of 20 or 25 on
NCB, on 35, on 45, on 50,
whatever discount there is, the discount
amount is shown in front. It is shown in this policy also,
but that amount is so high.  What
happens below is that you do
not understand on what basis
they have given the discount, that is the internal calculation of the company.
Now
why have I written 'be careful' because suppose if
you put NCB at 20, 25 or 35
and many times people put it deliberately saying
that I had taken the claim but I am
putting it deliberately, I will get the recovery done later,
my premium will be a little less, I will pay the
recovery money, then I can get it done in that
or if by mistake you
say that the no claim bonus is wrong
or you mistakenly
say that I did not take the claim,
maybe you may not know that
someone else in your family has taken the claim, you
think that you did not take the claim, you did not get the
NCB done and later if its recovery happens
then the premium for it can be
very high, normally
suppose if your policy is of 40000 then it is
possible that your NCB recovery can be from
20 to 25000 also but for other
companies  If we talk about it, the
percentage there is very much percentage wise
and you will see that, you will see
how they have applied the discount,
you will check the calculation
and you will see it, but it is very difficult to
check the NCB calculation in Go Digit
and I am telling you
not to make a mistake in NCB, if you make a mistake
then you may have to pay a premium of around 50 percent,
if your
no-cost bonus is around 25 to 35 percent
then even if it is less then you will have to pay more,
I am telling you,
definitely check the calculation or
you can also check your policy yourself, the
NCB calculation in your Go Digit policy is
completely different, let's talk about fuel
type, let's say in fuel type, if there is diesel,
petrol, electric, CNG then the
premium for all is different, so there is
no method of calculation as to
how much the premium will be, the
company will give you premium according to whatever your fuel is, the
premium varies according to the zone tooth,
according to the car model  The premium
is different depending on which car model you have,
suppose it is
diesel or petrol, then
your premium is different for all the things, sometimes it
also happens that you have bought the same car of the same year,
suppose you had bought two
cars together, the premium for both is
also different there, so there is
no single method of calculation, there are
many things, it is calculated on their behavior only
that how much the premium will be,
apart from this, if we talk about
support, then the company's website is god.com,
you can visit the company's website, you can
call on the company's number 1825 5956 here, if
you want to get any endorsement done, if
you want to make any changes, if you want to register a claim in the policy, then
you can call on this number,
you can email the
company @ god.com, you can directly email, if there is
any endorsement then you
can email the document, apart from that
whatsapp2 6061 234,
inside whatsapp2, so friends, the main thing now is that
we  Should you or anyone should take a policy or not, should
you or anyone should
take a policy from Goldt or not, so
friends, the way the company is working, the
way the company is giving the claim, we
talk to the customers, we
talk to the service center people, easily the company
gives the claim, there is no problem, till now
we have not seen any such issue in the service of the company,
brother, because of that we
reduce the rating of the company, so there is no such
problem, you
can easily take a claim in this company, you
can easily take a policy and you
should trust this company, by trusting you,
take the policy of the company, you will not face any problem here, so
friends, how did
you like our video, do tell us,
like our video while subscribing to our channel, if you feel
that the video is helpful for you, then
you can also share this video with your friends,
thank you.